atsu.edu 2016-07-29

# A.T. Still University - Policies - Privacy Policy

The following represents the information gathering and use practices of the ATSU website, [www.atsu.edu](http://www.atsu.edu/).

## Information gathering

A.T. Still University (ATSU) is committed to respecting your privacy. In general, you can visit ATSU on the Web without identifying yourself or revealing any personal information. In some areas, however, you may choose services that require you to provide us with information by which you can be identified. (For example, you can make requests and register to receive materials.) Once any personally identifiable information is received, you can be assured that it will only be used to support your relationship with ATSU.

We collect information about your visit to our website that will help us diagnose problems and to make our website more user-friendly. This information includes which portions of the site are most heavily used and which external websites or search terms are used to locate our site. While all cases are tracked for this information, all users remain anonymous and no personal information is collected.

## **Use of information**

ATSU uses the information collected from you to better understand your needs and to provide you with better service. Specifically, we use your information to help you complete a transaction, to communicate back to you, to update you on services and benefits, and to personalize our website for you.

ATSU will not sell, rent, or lease your personally identifiable information to others without your express permission. Unless we have your permission or are required by law, we will only share the personal data you provide online with authorized personnel within the institution. ATSU will not use or share the personally identifiable information provided to us online in ways unrelated to the ones described above without letting you know and offering you a choice.

## Security

ATSU is committed to ensuring the security of your information. To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the appropriate use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online. We use encryption when collecting or transferring sensitive data such as credit card information.

## Disclaimer

To assist users in finding related information, ATSU provides links to other websites. Once users have left the ATSU website and have entered another site, they are subject to the privacy policy of that site and ATSU cannot be responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such websites.

## Contacting the webmaster

ATSU provides this Online Privacy Statement to make you aware of our privacy policy and practices and of the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. To make this notice easy to find, we have made it available on our home page and several other pages throughout the site. If you have any questions about the practices of this site or your dealings with this site, you may contact ATSU’s web administrator at [webmaster@atsu.edu](mailto:webmaster@atsu.edu). If you have comments or questions about our privacy policy, please send them to [webmaster@atsu.edu](mailto:webmaster@atsu.edu).
